<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>bms4001_p1 on CityU-Bioinformatics</title>
    <link>/tags/bms4001_p1/</link>
    <description>Recent content in bms4001_p1 on CityU-Bioinformatics</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/bms4001_p1/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>ClinVar Database</title>
      <link>/tutorial/bms4001/clinvar-database/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tutorial/bms4001/clinvar-database/</guid>
      <description>Student Project done by:  Hau Sarah S R Hui Wing Yan Tsang Wui Kan Cody Au Yeung Hoi Ying  Their slides can be downloaded here
ClinVar is a freely accessible, public archive of reports of the relationships among human variations and phenotypes, with supporting evidence.
 Provides reports of the relationship among human variations and phenotypes, with supporting evidence Submission driven Submission of data can be from: 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gene Expression Omnibus</title>
      <link>/tutorial/bms4001/geo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tutorial/bms4001/geo/</guid>
      <description>Student Project done by:  Cheung Lung Chun, Joe Tsoi Ka Wai, Raymond Hu Yashi, Karen Kwok Kam Chak, George  Their slides can be downloaded here
Gene Expression Omnibus (GEO) is a public functional genomics data repository supporting MIAME-compliant data submissions. Array- and sequence-based data are accepted. Tools are provided to help users query and download experiments and curated gene expression profiles.
The three main goals of GEO are to:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>History of Computer</title>
      <link>/tutorial/bms4001/computer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tutorial/bms4001/computer/</guid>
      <description>Student Project done by:  Tang Hoi Man,Simon Cheung Tsz Chung,Derek Yau Ka Kit,Danny Chan Ching Yuen  Their slides can be downloaded here
The history of Computer. This part will briefly introduce the history of computer.
What is computer?  The word ‘Computer‘ is come from the word ‘compute’ which means to calculate. In the the early 17th century, computer is a job position that a person performing mathematical calculation for the company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>History of Internet</title>
      <link>/tutorial/bms4001/internet/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tutorial/bms4001/internet/</guid>
      <description>Student Project done by:  Lau Ching Man, Karen
 Au Ming Wai, Astrid
 Kwan Yuk Tip
 Chan Man Chung
  Their slides can be downloaded here
The Internet is a worldwide system of interconnected computer networks that use the TCP/IP set of network protocols to reach billions of users. The Internet began as a U.S Department of Defense network to link scientists and university professors around the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NIH Disaster Research Response (DR2)</title>
      <link>/tutorial/bms4001/nih/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tutorial/bms4001/nih/</guid>
      <description>Student Project done by:  LAI Ching Wun LAM Chun Kuen LEUNG Wai Ching THOMPSON Secily Aniela Marie  Their slides can be downloaded here
NIH Disaster Research Response (DR2) is the national framework for research on the medical and public health aspects of disasters and public health emergencies.
 Public health informatics database created by the National Institute of Environmental Health Sciences and the National Library of Medicine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UCSC Genome Browser</title>
      <link>/tutorial/bms4001/ucsc_gb/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tutorial/bms4001/ucsc_gb/</guid>
      <description>Student Project done by:  Chui Pui Man, Pui
 Lee Kam Yan, Kam
 Wong Yin Chung, Alex
 Yu Man Yee, Mandy
  Their slides can be downloaded here
UCSC Genome Browser  is a web-based tool that provides a fast, easy way to display a specific region of a genome assembly, along with dozens of aligned annotation tracks.
The browser features data from a large collection of vertebrates, model organisms, and selected invertebrate genomes.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>