<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bioinformatics Specific on CityU-Bioinformatics</title>
    <link>/journal/specific/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Bioinformatics Specific on CityU-Bioinformatics</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/journal/specific/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Algorithms for Molecular Biology</title>
      <link>/journal/specific/algorithms-for-molecular-biology/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/journal/specific/algorithms-for-molecular-biology/</guid>
      <description>Official Website
Algorithms for Molecular Biology publishes articles on novel algorithms for biological sequence and structure analysis, phylogeny reconstruction, and combinatorial algorithms and machine learning.
Areas of interest include but are not limited to: algorithms for RNA and protein structure analysis, gene prediction and genome analysis, comparative sequence analysis and alignment, phylogeny, gene expression, machine learning, and combinatorial algorithms.
Where appropriate, manuscripts should describe applications to real-world data. However, pure algorithm papers are also welcome if future applications to biological data are to be expected, or if they address complexity or approximation issues of novel computational problems in molecular biology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bioinformatics</title>
      <link>/journal/specific/bioinformatics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/journal/specific/bioinformatics/</guid>
      <description>Official Website
Bioinformatics is the leading journal in its field, Bioinformatics publishes the highest quality scientific papers and review articles of interest to academic and industrial researchers. It is a biweekly peer-reviewed scientific journal covering research and software in computational biology. It is the official journal of the International Society for Computational Biology (ISCB), together with PLOS Computational Biology.
Its main focus is on new developments in genome bioinformatics and computational biology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BMC Bioinformatics</title>
      <link>/journal/specific/bmc-bioinformatics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/journal/specific/bmc-bioinformatics/</guid>
      <description>Official Website
BMC Bioinformatics is an open access, peer-reviewed journal that considers articles on all aspects of the development, testing and novel application of computational and statistical methods for the modeling and analysis of all kinds of biological data, as well as other areas of computational biology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BMC Genomics</title>
      <link>/journal/specific/bmc-genomics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/journal/specific/bmc-genomics/</guid>
      <description>Official Website
BMC Genomics is an open access, peer-reviewed journal that considers articles on all aspects of genome-scale analysis, functional genomics, and proteomics.
All articles published by BMC Genomics are made freely and permanently accessible online immediately upon publication, without subscription charges or registration barriers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BMC Systems Biology</title>
      <link>/journal/specific/bmc-systems-biology/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/journal/specific/bmc-systems-biology/</guid>
      <description>Official Website
BMC Systems Biology filled a gap in what was a new research field, the journal was established in 2007 and is published by BioMed Central and it is a part of the BMC Series of journals.
BMC Systems Biology is an open access journal publishing original peer-reviewed research articles in experimental and theoretical aspects of the function of biological systems at the molecular, cellular or organismal level, in particular those addressing the engineering of biological systems, network modelling, quantitative analyses, integration of different levels of information and synthetic biology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Briefing in Bioinformatics</title>
      <link>/journal/specific/briefings-in-bioinformatics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/journal/specific/briefings-in-bioinformatics/</guid>
      <description>Official Website
Briefings in Bioinformatics is an international forum for researchers and educators in the life sciences. The journal will also be of interest to mathematicians, statisticians and computer scientists who apply their work to biological problems. The journal publishes reviews for the users of databases and analytical tools of contemporary genetics, molecular and systems biology and is unique in providing practical help and guidance to the non-specialist in computerized methodology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Journal of Computational Biology</title>
      <link>/journal/specific/journal-of-computational-biology/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/journal/specific/journal-of-computational-biology/</guid>
      <description>Official Website
Journal of Computational Biology is the leading journal covering the analysis, management, and visualization of cellular information at the molecular level. The Journal publishes peer-reviewed papers focusing on novel, cutting-edge methods in computational biology and bioinformatics.
Topics include: • Genomics • Mathematical modeling and simulation • Distributed and parallel biological computing • Designing biological databases • Pattern matching and pattern detection • Linking disparate databases and data • New tools for computational biology • Relational and object-oriented database technology for bioinformatics</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Journal of Mathematical Biology</title>
      <link>/journal/specific/journal-of-mathematical-biology/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/journal/specific/journal-of-mathematical-biology/</guid>
      <description>Official Website
Journal of Mathematical Biology is a peer-reviewed, mathematics journal, published by Springer Verlag. Founded in 1974, the journal publishes articles on mathematical biology. It is the official journal of the European Society for Mathematical and Theoretical Biology.
The aim of the Journal of Mathematical Biology is, on the one hand, to foster the contribution of mathematical modelling and reasoning to the understanding of biological systems and the explanation of biological phenomena, and, on the other hand, to be a forum for the presentation of biologically inspired problems of a mathematical nature.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Journal of Theoretical Biology</title>
      <link>/journal/specific/journal-of-theoretical-biology/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/journal/specific/journal-of-theoretical-biology/</guid>
      <description>Official Website
The Journal of Theoretical Biology is the leading forum for theoretical perspectives that give insight into biological processes.
It covers a very wide range of topics and is of interest to biologists in many areas of research, including:
 Brain and Neuroscience Cancer Growth and Treatment Cell Biology Developmental Biology Ecology Evolution Immunology, Infectious and non-infectious Diseases, Mathematical, Computational, Biophysical and Statistical Modeling Microbiology, Molecular Biology, and Biochemistry Networks and Complex Systems  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mathematical Biosciences</title>
      <link>/journal/specific/mathematical-biosciences/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/journal/specific/mathematical-biosciences/</guid>
      <description>Official Website
This leading international journal publishes research and expository papers on the formulation, analysis and solution of mathematical models in the biosciences.
The journal serves both mathematicians involved in solving model equations or in reaching conclusions that are testable in the real world, and biologists who are interested in forming mathematical models of biological processes and systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PLOS Computational Biology</title>
      <link>/journal/specific/plos-computational-biology/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/journal/specific/plos-computational-biology/</guid>
      <description>Official Website
By making connections through the application of computational methods among disparate areas of biology, PLOS Computational Biology provides substantial new insight into living systems at all scales, from the nano to the macro, and across multiple disciplines, from molecular science, neuroscience and physiology to ecology and population biology.
PLOS Computational Biology is an official journal of the International Society for Computational Biology (ISCB).
PLOS Computational Biology features works of exceptional significance that further our understanding of living systems at all scales—from molecules and cells, to patient populations and ecosystems—through the application of computational methods.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>