<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Resources on CityU-Bioinformatics</title>
    <link>/tags/resources/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Resources on CityU-Bioinformatics</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/resources/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Online Courses</title>
      <link>/tutorial/cou_new/online-courses/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tutorial/cou_new/online-courses/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Online Courses edx online courses  R Programming courses: Data Science related courses: Mechine Learning courses:  Coursera online courses  R Programming courses: Data Science related courses: Mechine Learning courses:    Online Courses There are many great online learning platforms that provide various elementary and advanced courses of R/Data science/R-packages. Most of those courses is free, but you can also choose some charged courses for specific needs or pay for a verified certificate of the courses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Other Resources</title>
      <link>/tutorial/res_new/sources/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tutorial/res_new/sources/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Bioconductor Recommended books Blogs/website International Society for Computational Biology (ISCB) Careers: How can I become a bioinformatics practitioner?   There are many great open sources website which contains tutorials, softwares, tools of bioinformatics field to help you get a great understanding of it and make effectively use of related softwares/tools.
Bioconductor Bioconductor is an open source, open development software project to provide tools for the analysis and comprehension of high-throughput genomic data.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>