<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Proteomics on CityU-Bioinformatics</title>
    <link>/tags/proteomics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Proteomics on CityU-Bioinformatics</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/proteomics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Immune System</title>
      <link>/too2/new_proteo/immune/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/too2/new_proteo/immune/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Immune System Analysis  Sequence-based B-cell Epitope Prediction Structure-based B-cell Epitope Prediction Antibody Structure Prediction MHC Class I Epitope Prediction MHC Class II Epitope Prediction  Flow Cytometry  Cell Population Identification Data Repositories Utilities  Mass Cytometry Peptide Array Analysis Find more tools: OMICTOOLS   Immune System Analysis Immunoinformatics involves the application of computational methods to immunological problems. Prediction of B- and T-cell epitopes has long been the focus of immunoinformatics, given the potential translational implications, and many tools have been developed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Membrane Protein</title>
      <link>/too2/new_proteo/membrane/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/too2/new_proteo/membrane/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Membrane Protein Analysis  Membrane Protein-protein Docking Membrane Simulation Transmembrane Beta-barrel Prediction Transmembrane Helix Prediction Function Membrane Protein  FRAP Find more tools: OMICTOOLS   Membrane Protein Analysis Membrane and transmembrane proteins are key component of cell signaling. Their configuration, folding, or activity depend on several biochemical factors that can be predicted by specific software.
Membrane Protein-protein Docking Membrane Simulation Transmembrane Beta-barrel Prediction Transmembrane Helix Prediction Function Membrane Protein FRAP Top</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prediction of Protein Structure</title>
      <link>/too2/new_proteo/structure/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/too2/new_proteo/structure/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Primary structure    ProtParam COILS   Secondary structure    PredictProtein PSIPRED   tertiary structure    Phyre Swiss-PdbViewer   Find more tools: OMICTOOLS   Primary structure Protein primary structure is the linear sequence of amino acids in a peptide or protein. By convention, the primary structure of a protein is reported starting from the amino-terminal (N) end to the carboxyl-terminal &amp;copy; end.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Protein Interactions</title>
      <link>/too2/new_proteo/interactions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/too2/new_proteo/interactions/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Protein Interactions Analysis  Protein-DNA Interaction Prediction Protein-RNA Interaction Prediction Pocket Detection Drug-target Interaction Prediction Protein-protein Interaction Prediction Protein-ligand Docking Protein-protein Docking  FRET Find more tools: OMICTOOLS   Protein Interactions Analysis Proteins interact with nucleic acids, other proteins, ligands, metal ions, to exert their biological functions. Mass-spectrometry and protein chips have revolutionized the field of proteomics and the study of protein interactions to a wider scale, which require specific tools for their analyses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Protein Sequence/Expression</title>
      <link>/too2/new_proteo/pro_seq/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/too2/new_proteo/pro_seq/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Protein Sequence Analysis  Amino Acid Repeat Prediction  RADAR REPRO  Subcellular Localizaton Prediction  TargetP pRoloc  Protein Clustering  CD-HIT USEARCH   MS-based (Mass Spectrometry) untargeted Proteomics  2D gel Image Analysis  digeR Plasmo2D  In Silico Analysis  OpenMS multiplierz  Phosphorylation Site Assignment  Ascore Phosphonormalizer  PTM Identification  PIQED SUMmOn  Glycosylation Identification  SugarQb MAGIC   MS-based Metaproteomics    Unipept MPA   Antibody Array Analysis    PANDA   Find more tools: OMICTOOLS   Protein Sequence Analysis Protein sequence analysis tools are used to predict specific functions, activities, origin, or localization of proteins based on their amino-acid sequence.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>