<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Proteomics on CityU-Bioinformatics</title>
    <link>/tags/proteomics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Proteomics on CityU-Bioinformatics</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/proteomics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Immune System</title>
      <link>/too2/new_proteo/immune/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/too2/new_proteo/immune/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Immune System Analysis  Sequence-based B-cell Epitope Prediction  ABCpred BepiPred  Structure-based B-cell Epitope Prediction  LYRA  MHC Class I Epitope Prediction  ProPred1 GradDock  MHC Class II Epitope Prediction  HLAMatchmaker ProPred   Flow Cytometry  Cell Population Identification  FCS Express FlowJo   Mass Cytometry  SPADE (Spanning tree Progression of Density normalized Events viSNE | Data visualization : Flow cytometry  Find more tools: OMICTOOLS   Immune System Analysis Immunoinformatics involves the application of computational methods to immunological problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Membrane Protein</title>
      <link>/too2/new_proteo/membrane/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/too2/new_proteo/membrane/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Membrane Protein Analysis  Membrane Simulation  CHARMM-GUI Membrane Builder | Membrane simulation : Membrane protein analysis  Transmembrane Beta-barrel Prediction  PROFtmb | Transmembrane beta-barrel prediction : Membrane protein analysis PRED-TMBB | Transmembrane beta-barrel prediction : Membrane protein analysis  Transmembrane Helix Prediction  CCTOP | Consensus Constrained TOPology prediction SignalP   FRAP    easy-FRAP | FRAP : Laser scanning microscopy PyFRAP | Python Fluorescence Recovery After Photobleaching   Find more tools: OMICTOOLS   Membrane Protein Analysis Membrane and transmembrane proteins are key component of cell signaling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prediction of Protein Structure</title>
      <link>/too2/new_proteo/structure/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/too2/new_proteo/structure/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Primary structure  ProtParam COILS  Secondary structure  PredictProtein PSIPRED  tertiary structure  Phyre Swiss-PdbViewer  Find more tools: OMICTOOLS   Primary structure Protein primary structure is the linear sequence of amino acids in a peptide or protein. By convention, the primary structure of a protein is reported starting from the amino-terminal (N) end to the carboxyl-terminal &amp;copy; end. Protein biosynthesis is most commonly performed by ribosomes in cells.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Protein Interactions</title>
      <link>/too2/new_proteo/interactions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/too2/new_proteo/interactions/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Protein Interactions Analysis  Protein-DNA Interaction Prediction  LigParGen | Protein-ligand docking : Protein interaction analysis DBSI | DNA Binding Site Identifier  Protein-RNA Interaction Prediction  HADDOCK | High Ambiguity Driven protein-protein DOCKing Global Score | Protein-RNA interactions  Drug-target Interaction Prediction  Open Targets | Drug-target interaction prediction : Protein interaction analysis PiHelper | Drug-target interaction prediction : Protein interaction analysis  Protein-protein Interaction Prediction  mentha | Protein-protein interaction prediction : Protein interaction analysis compPASS | comparative proteomic analysis software suite  Protein-ligand Docking  UCSF Chimera  Protein-protein Docking  PIPER | Protein-protein docking : Protein interaction analysis HADDOCK | High Ambiguity Driven protein-protein DOCKing   Find more tools: OMICTOOLS   Protein Interactions Analysis Proteins interact with nucleic acids, other proteins, ligands, metal ions, to exert their biological functions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Protein Sequence/Expression</title>
      <link>/too2/new_proteo/pro_seq/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/too2/new_proteo/pro_seq/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Protein Sequence Analysis  Amino Acid Repeat Prediction  RADAR REPRO  Subcellular Localizaton Prediction  TargetP pRoloc  Protein Clustering  CD-HIT USEARCH   MS-based (Mass Spectrometry) untargeted Proteomics  2D gel Image Analysis  digeR Plasmo2D  In Silico Analysis  OpenMS multiplierz  Phosphorylation Site Assignment  Ascore Phosphonormalizer  PTM Identification  PIQED SUMmOn  Glycosylation Identification  SugarQb MAGIC   MS-based Metaproteomics    Unipept MPA   Antibody Array Analysis    PANDA   Find more tools: OMICTOOLS   Protein Sequence Analysis Protein sequence analysis tools are used to predict specific functions, activities, origin, or localization of proteins based on their amino-acid sequence.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>