<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>BMS4001:Medical Informatics and Laboratory Management on CityU-Bioinformatics</title>
    <link>/tutorial/bms4001/</link>
    <description>Recent content in BMS4001:Medical Informatics and Laboratory Management on CityU-Bioinformatics</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tutorial/bms4001/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>History of Computer</title>
      <link>/tutorial/bms4001/computer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tutorial/bms4001/computer/</guid>
      <description>Student Project done by:  Tang Hoi Man,Simon Cheung Tsz Chung,Derek Yau Ka Kit,Danny Chan Ching Yuen  Their slides can be downloaded here
The history of Computer. This part will briefly introduce the history of computer.
What is computer?  The word ‘Computer‘ is come from the word ‘compute’ which means to calculate. In the the early 17th century, computer is a job position that a person performing mathematical calculation for the company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>History of Internet</title>
      <link>/tutorial/bms4001/internet/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tutorial/bms4001/internet/</guid>
      <description>Student Project done by:  Lau Ching Man, Karen
 Au Ming Wai, Astrid
 Kwan Yuk Tip
 Chan Man Chung
  Their slides can be downloaded here
The Internet is a worldwide system of interconnected computer networks that use the TCP/IP set of network protocols to reach billions of users. The Internet began as a U.S Department of Defense network to link scientists and university professors around the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ClinVar Database</title>
      <link>/tutorial/bms4001/clinvar-database/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tutorial/bms4001/clinvar-database/</guid>
      <description>Student Project done by:  Hau Sarah S R Hui Wing Yan Tsang Wui Kan Cody Au Yeung Hoi Ying  Their slides can be downloaded here
ClinVar is a freely accessible, public archive of reports of the relationships among human variations and phenotypes, with supporting evidence.
 Provides reports of the relationship among human variations and phenotypes, with supporting evidence Submission driven Submission of data can be from: 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NIH Disaster Research Response (DR2)</title>
      <link>/tutorial/bms4001/nih/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tutorial/bms4001/nih/</guid>
      <description>Student Project done by:  LAI Ching Wun LAM Chun Kuen LEUNG Wai Ching THOMPSON Secily Aniela Marie  Their slides can be downloaded here
NIH Disaster Research Response (DR2) is the national framework for research on the medical and public health aspects of disasters and public health emergencies.
 Public health informatics database created by the National Institute of Environmental Health Sciences and the National Library of Medicine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UCSC Genome Browser</title>
      <link>/tutorial/bms4001/ucsc_gb/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tutorial/bms4001/ucsc_gb/</guid>
      <description>Student Project done by:  Chui Pui Man, Pui
 Lee Kam Yan, Kam
 Wong Yin Chung, Alex
 Yu Man Yee, Mandy
  Their slides can be downloaded here
UCSC Genome Browser  is a web-based tool that provides a fast, easy way to display a specific region of a genome assembly, along with dozens of aligned annotation tracks.
The browser features data from a large collection of vertebrates, model organisms, and selected invertebrate genomes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gene Expression Omnibus</title>
      <link>/tutorial/bms4001/geo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tutorial/bms4001/geo/</guid>
      <description>Student Project done by:  Cheung Lung Chun, Joe Tsoi Ka Wai, Raymond Hu Yashi, Karen Kwok Kam Chak, George  Their slides can be downloaded here
Gene Expression Omnibus (GEO) is a public functional genomics data repository supporting MIAME-compliant data submissions. Array- and sequence-based data are accepted. Tools are provided to help users query and download experiments and curated gene expression profiles.
The three main goals of GEO are to:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colorectal Cancer Risk Assessment Tool</title>
      <link>/tutorial/bms4001/colorectal/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tutorial/bms4001/colorectal/</guid>
      <description>Student Project done by:  Fu Wing Shing Ko Ka Yam Lam Ho Hon John Kelly Lau Angie Luu Si Xin  Their slides can be downloaded here
The Colorectal Cancer Risk Assessment Tool was designed for use by doctors and other health providers with their patients. If you are not a health provider, take these results to your doctor or other health provider to discuss your personal risk of colorectal cancer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Breast Cancer Risk Assessment Tool</title>
      <link>/tutorial/bms4001/breast/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tutorial/bms4001/breast/</guid>
      <description>Student Project done by:  CHENG Chun Yi IP Wai Yi PONG Yin Chung Charles SO Wai Yin  Their slides can be downloaded here
The Breast Cancer Risk Assessment Tool is an interactive tool designed by scientists at the National Cancer Institute (NCI) and the National Surgical Adjuvant Breast and Bowel Project (NSABP) to estimate a woman&amp;rsquo;s risk of developing invasive breast cancer.
Breast cancer: malignant tumor cells originates from the breast that attacks the nearby healthy tissue, and it can spread outside to the other tissue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PICO (Patient, Intervention, Comparison, Outcome)</title>
      <link>/tutorial/bms4001/pico/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tutorial/bms4001/pico/</guid>
      <description>Student Project done by:  Chan Ching Yuen Yau Ka Kit, Danny Cheung Tsz Chung, Derek Tang Hoi Man, Simon  Their slides can be downloaded here
The PICO is a technique used in evidence based practice to frame and answer a clinical or health care related question. The PICO framework is also used to develop literature search strategies. The PICO acronym stands for
 P – patient, problem or population I – intervention C – comparison, control or comparator[5] O – outcome  Official Website</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Repository for Informed Decision Making (RIDeM)</title>
      <link>/tutorial/bms4001/ridem/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tutorial/bms4001/ridem/</guid>
      <description>Student Project done by:  Lau Ching Man
 Au Ming Wai, Astrid
 Kwan Yuk Tip
 Chan Man Chung
  Their slides can be downloaded here
RIDeM is one of the LHNCBC Clinical Decision Support projects. The long-term goal of the Repository for Informed Decision Making is to provide access to key facts needed to support clinical decision making. The facts are extracted from biomedical literature and clinical text sources.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State Tobacco Activities Tracking and Evaluation (STATE) System</title>
      <link>/tutorial/bms4001/state/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tutorial/bms4001/state/</guid>
      <description>Student Project done by:  Au Yeung Hoi Ying, Cody Hau Sarah S R Hui Wing Yan, Renee Tsang Wui Kan, Ken  Their slides can be downloaded here
State Tobacco Activities Tracking and Evaluation (STATE) System is an electronic data warehouse/interactive application.
 Contains up-tp-date and historical state-level data Tobacco use prevention + control Integrates data Provide 3 types of comprehensive summary data Facilitate research + consistent data interpretation  Purpose of STATE System  To reduce the incidence of tobacco related disease and preventable death To suport the tracking + monitoring of key data measures Disseminate information via the Internet on an annual basis Maintain key data measures collected from various data sources in one information warehouse Support production of dynamic reports by topic  Target Users of STATE System These materials provide public health officials and researchers with knowledge of a comprehensive tool for tobacco research, and public health professionals can use these systems&amp;rsquo; broad range of data and advanced reporting features to disseminate data related to tobacco control.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US CDC FluView Interactive</title>
      <link>/tutorial/bms4001/us_cdc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tutorial/bms4001/us_cdc/</guid>
      <description>Student Project done by:  LAI Ching Wun LAM Chun Kuen LEUNG Wai Ching Secily Thompson  Their slides can be downloaded here
US CDC FluView Interactive. The CDC FluView report provides weekly influenza surveillance information in the United States. These applications were developed to enhance the weekly FluView report by better facilitating communication about influenza with the public health community, clinicians, scientists, and the general public. This series of dynamic visualizations allow any Internet user to access influenza information collected by CDC’s monitoring systems.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>