<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Conferences on CityU-Bioinformatics</title>
    <link>/journal/conferences/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Conferences on CityU-Bioinformatics</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/journal/conferences/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Research in Computational Molecular Biology (RECOMB)</title>
      <link>/journal/conferences/acm-recomb/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/journal/conferences/acm-recomb/</guid>
      <description>Official Website
The RECOMB conference series was founded in 1997 to provide a scientific forum for theoretical advances in computational biology and their applications in molecular biology and medicine. The conference solicits research contributions from all areas of computational molecular biology.
Typical but not exclusive topics of interest include:
 Molecular sequence analysis Recognition of genes and regulatory elements Molecular evolution Gene expression Biological networks Sequencing and genotyping techniques Genomics Population genetics Systems biology Imaging Computational proteomics Molecular structural biology  The origins of the conference came from the mathematical and computational side of the field, and there remains a focus on computational advances.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Asia Pacific Bioinformatics Conference (APBC)</title>
      <link>/journal/conferences/apbc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/journal/conferences/apbc/</guid>
      <description>Official Website
The Asia Pacific Bioinformatics Conference (APBC) series is an annual international forum for exploring research, development and novel applications in the field of Bioinformatics. The aim of APBC is to bring together academia and industry to share knowledge and experiences, and to showcase innovations and achievements. It has been held since 2003 around Asia Pacific Regions
Accepted papers will be invited to be published in IEEE/ACM TCBB, BMC Bioinformatics, BMC Genomics, BMC Systems Biology, and Computational Biology and Chemistry following each journal’s publication policy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basel Computational Biology Conference (BC2)</title>
      <link>/journal/conferences/bc2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/journal/conferences/bc2/</guid>
      <description>Official Website
The Basel Computational Biology Conference (stylized as [BC]2) is a scientific meeting on the subjects of bioinformatics and computational biology. It covers a wide spectrum of disciplines, including bioinformatics, computational biology, genomics, computational structural biology, and systems biology.
BC2 Basel Computational Biology conference is the scientific symposium of the SIB Swiss Institute of Bioinformatics, organized in collaboration with the Biozentrum University of Basel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bioinformatics and Bioengineering (BIBE)</title>
      <link>/journal/conferences/bibe/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/journal/conferences/bibe/</guid>
      <description>Official Website
The series of BIBE Conferences was found in 2000 and BIBE is the first leading Conference of its kind in IEEE/Internationally inspiring others to follow its path. The annual IEEE International Conference on Bioinformatics and Bioengineering aims at building synergy between Bioinformatics and Bioengineering/Biomedical, two complementary disciplines that hold great promise for the advancement of research and development in complex medical and biological systems, agriculture, environment, public health, drug design.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Annual International Computing and Combinatorics Conference (COCOON)</title>
      <link>/journal/conferences/cocoon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/journal/conferences/cocoon/</guid>
      <description>Official Website
Original research papers in the areas of algorithms, theory of computation, computational complexity, and combinatorics related to computing are solicited. In addition to theoretical results, they are particularly interested in submissions that report on experimental and applied research of general algorithmic interest. Special consideration will be given to research that is motivated by real-world problems. Experimental and applied papers are expected to show convincingly the usefulness and efficiency of the algorithms discussed in a practical setting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Annual Symposium on Combinatorial Pattern Matching (CPM)</title>
      <link>/journal/conferences/cpm/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/journal/conferences/cpm/</guid>
      <description>Official Website
Papers on original research unpublished elsewhere in all areas related to combinatorial pattern matching and its applications are welcome.
These include, but not limit to
 Bioinformatics and computational biology Coding and data compression Combinatorics on words Data mining Information retrieval Natural language processing Pattern discovery String algorithms String processing in databases Symbolic computing Text searching and indexing  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>European Conference on Computational Biology (ECCB)</title>
      <link>/journal/conferences/eccb/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/journal/conferences/eccb/</guid>
      <description>Official Website
It is the main computational biology event in Europe and will welcome scientists working in a variety of disciplines, including bioinformatics, computational biology, biology, medicine, and systems biology. Participating in ECCB will be the perfect opportunity to keep pace with cutting edge research, and to network with members of ECCB community.
The conference covers computational methods for molecular biology that arise in the context of genomics and proteomics technologies in the fields of molecular biology, molecular medicine and pharmaceutics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The IEEE Engineering in Medicine and Biology Society (EMBC)</title>
      <link>/journal/conferences/embc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/journal/conferences/embc/</guid>
      <description>Official Website
The IEEE Engineering in Medicine and Biology Society is pleased to announce the 40th International Engineering in Medicine and Biology Conference, to be held in Honolulu, Hawaii from July 17-21, 2018.
A broad array of scientific tracks will cover diverse topics of cutting-edge research and innovation in biomedical engineering, healthcare technology R&amp;amp;D, translational clinical research, technology transfer and entrepreneurship, and biomedical engineering education. In addition to the high-profile keynotes, the conference program will feature mini symposia, workshops, invited sessions, oral and poster sessions, sessions for students and young professions, sessions for clinicians and entrepreneurs, and exhibits from vendors and universities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>International Conference on Bioinformatics (InCoB)</title>
      <link>/journal/conferences/incob/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/journal/conferences/incob/</guid>
      <description>Official Website
International Conference on Bioinformatics (InCoB) is the annual conference of Asia-Pacific Bioinformatics Network (APBioNet) that showcases the latest research and technologies in all areas of bioinformatics. Since 2002, InCoB has been attended by practitioners from both biology fields and computing backgrounds in the Asia-Pacific region, and also from other regions.
Originally organised by coordination between the Asia Pacific Bioinformatics Network (APBioNet) and the Thailand National Center for Genetic Engineering and Biotechnology (BIOTEC) in 2002, the meeting has since been the flagship conference of the APBioNet, where APBioNet&amp;rsquo;s Annual General Meeting is held.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intelligent Systems for Molecular Biology (ISMB)</title>
      <link>/journal/conferences/ismb/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/journal/conferences/ismb/</guid>
      <description>Official Website
Intelligent Systems for Molecular Biology (ISMB) is an annual academic conference on the subjects of bioinformatics and computational biology organised by the International Society for Computational Biology (ISCB). The principal focus of the conference is on the development and application of advanced computational methods for biological problems. The conference has been held every year since 1993 and has grown to become one of the largest and most prestigious meetings in these fields, hosting over 2,000 delegates in 2004.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pacific Symposium on Biocomputing (PSB)</title>
      <link>/journal/conferences/pacific-symposium-on-biocomputing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/journal/conferences/pacific-symposium-on-biocomputing/</guid>
      <description>Official Website
The Pacific Symposium on Biocomputing (PSB) is a multidisciplinary scientific meeting held annually since 1996. The conference is to presentation and discuss research in the theory and application of computational methods for biology. Papers and presentations are peer reviewed and published.
PSB brings together researchers from the US and the Asian Pacific nations, to exchange research results and address open issues in all aspects of computational biology. PSB is a forum for the presentation of work in databases, algorithms, interfaces, visualization, modeling, and other computational methods, as applied to biological problems, with emphasis on applications in data-rich areas of molecular biology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Workshop on Algorithms in Bioinformatics (WABI)</title>
      <link>/journal/conferences/wabi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/journal/conferences/wabi/</guid>
      <description>Official Website
All research in algorithmic work in bioinformatics, computational biology and systems biology. The emphasis is mainly on discrete algorithms and machine-learning methods that address important problems in molecular biology, that are founded on sound models, that are computationally efficient, and that have been implemented and tested in simulations and on real datasets. The goal is to present recent research results, including significant work-in-progress, and to identify and explore directions of future research.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>