<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Too2s on CityU-Bioinformatics</title>
    <link>/too2/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Too2s on CityU-Bioinformatics</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/too2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Bioimaging</title>
      <link>/too2/new_pheno/bioimaging/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/too2/new_pheno/bioimaging/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Microscopic Phenotype Analysis  Microscopic Image Formats Management Education PheWAS  Image Preprocessing  Image Acquisition Image Enhancement Image Deconvolution  Image processing  Image Simulation Image Segmentation Image Registration  Laser Scanning Microscopy  FISH Colocalization Analysis 3D Image Analysis  Conventional Fluorescence microscopy  High-throughput Screening Cell Phenotyping Mitochondrial Network Analysis  Super-resolution Imaging  Morphometric Analysis Single Molecule Detection and Localization FLIM data Analysis FRET Data Analysis  Cryo-EM  Neuron Tracing Single Particle Analysis  Find more tools: OMICTOOLS   Microscopic Phenotype Analysis Microscopic phenotype analysis deals with all tools usefull for describing, identifying or classifying phenotypes at microscopic scale.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DNA Modifications</title>
      <link>/too2/new_epi/modifications/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/too2/new_epi/modifications/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  DNA modification analysis  DNA Methylation Prediction DNA Methylation Deconvolution  DNA methylation array analysis  Differential Methylation Site Detection Differential Methylation region Detection  Enrichment Analysis  Over-representation analysis Gene set enrichment analysis Topology enrichment analysis  Bisulfite Sequencing Data Analysis (BS-seq analysis)  Differential Methylation region Detection Methylation Annotation EWAS  Find more tools: OMICTOOLS   DNA modification analysis Whole genome DNA methylation detection is one of the most important part of epigenetics research.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Genome Annotation</title>
      <link>/too2/new_geno/anno/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/too2/new_geno/anno/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Genome Annotation  Gene Ontology Annotation  BLASTX Blast2GO  GO Semantic Similarity Analysis  G-SESAME | Gene Semantic Similarity Analysis and Measurement Tools clusterProfiler | GO semantic similarity analysis : Genome annotation GOToolBox | GO semantic similarity analysis : DNA sequence analysis SML-Toolkit | Semantic Measures Library Toolkit  Promoter Predication  FirstEF | First Exon Finder CpGpromoter PROmiRNA  Annotation Workflows  RAST | Rapid Annotation using Subsystem Technology Prokka | Annotation workflows BlastKOALA   Find more tools: OMICTOOLS   Genome Annotation Genome annotation is a key process for identifying the coding and non-coding regions of a genome, gene locations and functions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Metabolic Profiles</title>
      <link>/too2/new_meta/profiles/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/too2/new_meta/profiles/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Metabolic profiles analysis  Metabolic Network analysis mGWAS Metabolite enrichment analysis  MS-based untargeted Metabolomics  Metabolic Network analysis mGWAS Metabolite enrichment analysis  NMR-based Metabolomics/MS-based targeted metabolomics  Spectral corrections Spectral deconvolution Chemometric analysis Metabolite identification  Find more tools: OMICTOOLS   Metabolic profiles analysis The further development of spectroscopic and spectrometric tools for high throughput analyses of selected biochemical pathways is crucial to the acquisition of metabolome data sets of sufficient quality for metabonomics and metabolomics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Protein Sequence/Expression</title>
      <link>/too2/new_proteo/pro_seq/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/too2/new_proteo/pro_seq/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Protein Sequence Analysis  Amino Acid Repeat Prediction Subcellular Localizaton Prediction T3S effector Prediction Protein Clustering SDS Prediction  MS-based (Mass Spectrometry) untargeted Proteomics  2D gel Image Analysis In Silico Analysis Phosphorylation Site Assignment PTM Identification Glycosylation Identification  MS-based Metaproteomics Antibody Array Analysis Proteogenomics Analysis Find more tools: OMICTOOLS   Protein Sequence Analysis Protein sequence analysis tools are used to predict specific functions, activities, origin, or localization of proteins based on their amino-acid sequence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RNA Transcription</title>
      <link>/too2/new_trans/transcription/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/too2/new_trans/transcription/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Transcription analysis  Prognostic Biomarker Identification Region Discrimination Gene co-expression prediction Gene regulatory network inference Gene set enrichment analysis Over-representation analysisi  RNA-seq analysis  Read count Known transcript quantification Gene fusion detection Prognostic biomarker identification Differential expression Alternative splicing events identification  CAGE Analysis  TSS detection De novo motif discovery  Gene expression array analysis  Differential expression detection Time course Meta-analysis  Metatranscriptomic sequencing analysis  Prediction-base Taxonomic Homology-Based Taxonomic  Find more tools: OMICTOOLS   Transcription analysis Transcript abundance is in many ways an extraordinary phenotype, with special attributes that confer particular importance on an understanding of its genetics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DNA Structure</title>
      <link>/too2/new_geno/dnastr/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/too2/new_geno/dnastr/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  DNA Structure  Shape prediction  do_x3dna 3DNA DINAMelt DNAshape  R-loop forming sequence prediction  QmRLFS-finder  DNA Structure Database  R-loopDB | R-loop forming sequence databases  Small-angle Scattering  AXES FoXS AquaSAXS   Find more tools: OMICTOOLS   DNA Structure DNA molecules exist in many different conformations, including A-DNA, B-DNA, or Z-DNA forms, which depend on the nucleotide sequence, hydratation level, presence of metal ions, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lipidomics</title>
      <link>/too2/new_meta/lipidomics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/too2/new_meta/lipidomics/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Transcription analysis Lipidomics Databases MS-based untargeted lipidomics MS-based targeted lipidomics Find more tools: OMICTOOLS   Transcription analysis Transcript abundance is in many ways an extraordinary phenotype, with special attributes that confer particular importance on an understanding of its genetics. The primary transformative potential of genome-wide gene expression genetics is the sheer number of traits — thousands — that can be assayed simultaneously.
Lipidomics Databases Development of databases and the related bioinformatics tools has become an essential part of the omics studies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Low-level RNA detection</title>
      <link>/too2/new_trans/lowlevel/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/too2/new_trans/lowlevel/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Low-level RNA detection scRNA-seq analysis  Noise reduction Transcript quantification Cell lineage and pseudotime inference Dimensionality reduction  Single-cell qPCR dPCR Find more tools: OMICTOOLS   Low-level RNA detection scRNA-seq analysis The development of high-throughput RNA sequencing (RNA-seq) at the single-cell level has already led to profound new discoveries in biology, ranging from the identification of novel cell types to the study of global patterns of stochastic gene expression.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Medical Imaging</title>
      <link>/too2/new_pheno/medicalimage/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/too2/new_pheno/medicalimage/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Medical Phrnotype Analysis  Clinical Risk Prediction Personal Health Record Analysis Clinical Simulation  Magnetic Resonance Imaging (MRI)  Image modelization DICOM files management  Computerized Tomography Scan Imaging (CT)  Phantom Imaging Image Format Management  Nuclear Medicine Imaging  3D Image Reconstruction Kinetic Analysis  Ultrasonic Imaging  Image Acquisition Image Visualization  Find more tools: OMICTOOLS   Medical Phrnotype Analysis Macroscopic phenotype analysis deals with all tools usefull for describing, identifying or classifying phenotypes at macroscopic scale.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nucleosome Positioning</title>
      <link>/too2/new_epi/position/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/too2/new_epi/position/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Nucleosome Positioning MNase-seq analysis ATAC-seq analysis Find more tools: OMIVTOOLS   Nucleosome Positioning MNase-seq analysis The technology of micrococcal nuclease (MNase) digestion combined with high-throughput sequencing (MNase-seq) is a powerful method to map the genome-wide distribution of nucleosome occupancy (Mavrich et al., 2008; Schones et al., 2008; Jiang and Pugh, 2009). Source text: Chen et al., 2014.
ATAC-seq analysis ATAC-seq allows simultaneous interrogation of factor occupancy, nucleosome positions in regulatory sites, and chromatin accessibility genome wide by considering the position of insertion and the distribution of insert lengths captured during the transposition reaction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prediction of Protein Structure</title>
      <link>/too2/new_proteo/structure/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/too2/new_proteo/structure/</guid>
      <description>This part may contains the following tools: (Will be filled in the future)
Primary structure ProtParam COILS Secondary structure PredictProtein PSIPRED tertiary structure Phyre Swiss-PdbViewer Top
Find more tools: OMICTOOLS Image Citation</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Computational Neuroinformatics</title>
      <link>/too2/new_pheno/neuroinformatics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/too2/new_pheno/neuroinformatics/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Biological Steps  Realistic Neuronal Network Modelling Compartment Neuron modelling  File Manipulation  Model Files Conversion Model Files Visualization Model Building  Database Find more tools: OMICTOOLS   Modelling in computational neuroscience is becoming a crucial tool for understanding how experimentally observed properties of neural systems emerge from lower-level biophysical processes. In the same way that processing of information happens at multiple physical scales in the nervous system, software applications have been created which specialize in modelling different aspects of neurons and networks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DNA-Protein Interactions</title>
      <link>/too2/new_epi/dna_pro/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/too2/new_epi/dna_pro/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  HT-SELEX Analysis DNase-seq Analysis ChIP-seq Analysis  De novo assembly Peak calling Differential peak calling De novo motif discovery  Find more tools: OMICTOOLS   DNA-binding proteins are proteins that have DNA-binding domains and thus have a specific or general affinity for single- or double-stranded DNA. Sequence-specific DNA-binding proteins generally interact with the major groove of B-DNA, because it exposes more functional groups that identify a base pair.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drug Discovery</title>
      <link>/too2/new_meta/drug/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/too2/new_meta/drug/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Drug Discovery  Chemical Enrichment Analysis Drug-drug interaction prediction Ligand-based Virtual Screening Drug Repositioning Chemical Toxicity Molecular editors  Find more tools: OMICTOOLS   Drug Discovery In the fields of medicine, biotechnology and pharmacology, drug discovery is the process by which new candidate medications are discovered. Historically, drugs were discovered through identifying the active ingredient from traditional remedies or by serendipitous discovery. Later chemical libraries of synthetic small molecules, natural products or extracts were screened in intact cells or whole organisms to identify substances that have a desirable therapeutic effect in a process known as classical pharmacology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Genome Editing</title>
      <link>/too2/new_geno/edit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/too2/new_geno/edit/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Genome Editing  CRISPR/Cas9 sgRNA Design  CRISPR design GuideScan E-CRISP CRISPRscan  TALEN design  TALE-NT TALEN Targeter  ZFN Design  Zinc Finger Tools ZifNN ZFN-Site  CRISPR/Cas9 Screen Analysis  CREATE | CRISPR-enabled trackable genome engineering MAGeCK | Model-based Analysis of Genome-wide CRISPR/Cas9 Knockout MAGeCK-VISPR caRpools | CRISPR-AnalyzeR for pooled screens  Genome Editing Database  Find more tools: OMICTOOLS   Genome Editing Programmable nucleases - including zinc-finger nucleases (ZFNs), transcription activator-like effector nucleases (TALENs) and RNA-guided engineered nucleases (RGENs) derived from the bacterial clustered regularly interspaced short palindromic repeat (CRISPR)-Cas (CRISPR-associated) system - enable targeted genetic modifications in cultured cells, as well as in whole animals and plants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Immune System</title>
      <link>/too2/new_proteo/immune/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/too2/new_proteo/immune/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Immune System Analysis  Sequence-based B-cell Epitope Prediction Structure-based B-cell Epitope Prediction Antibody Structure Prediction MHC Class I Epitope Prediction MHC Class II Epitope Prediction  Flow Cytometry  Cell Population Identification Data Repositories Utilities  Mass Cytometry Peptide Array Analysis Find more tools: OMICTOOLS   Immune System Analysis Immunoinformatics involves the application of computational methods to immunological problems. Prediction of B- and T-cell epitopes has long been the focus of immunoinformatics, given the potential translational implications, and many tools have been developed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RNA Modifications</title>
      <link>/too2/new_trans/rnamodification/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/too2/new_trans/rnamodification/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  RNA Modifications Analysis  Protein-binding Region Prediction RNA Editing Prediction Alternative Splicing Annotation RNA Methylation Prediction  Methylated RNA Immunoprecipitation Sequencing Data Analysis (MeRIP-seq Analysis)  Spliced Read Alignment Peak Calling De novo motif discovery  Degradome-seq Analysis Find more tools: OMICTOOLS   RNA Modifications Analysis From a biosynthetic point of view, the roughly 100 known different RNA nucleotide modifications can be easily divided according to their complexity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Metabolic Engineering</title>
      <link>/too2/new_meta/engineer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/too2/new_meta/engineer/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Biological Steps  Constraint based methods Metabolic pathway prediction Strain design Thermodynamics  Network Analysis  Genome-scale Metabolic Reconstruction  13C-fluxomics Find more tools: OMICTOOLS   Growing concerns over limited fossil resources and associated environmental problems are motivating the development of sustainable processes for the production of chemicals, fuels and materials from renewable resources. Metabolic engineering is a key enabling technology for transforming microorganisms into efficient cell factories for these compounds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Neorophysiology</title>
      <link>/too2/new_pheno/neurophysiology/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/too2/new_pheno/neurophysiology/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Neurophysiology Analysis Clinical Eletrophysiology  Data Acquisition Spike Sorting Image Data Analysis Data Management and Annotation  Patch-clamp Find more tools: OMICTOOLS   Neurophysiology Analysis Clinical Eletrophysiology Electrophysiology, the &amp;lsquo;gold standard&amp;rsquo; for investigating neuronal signalling, is being challenged by a new generation of optical probes. Together with new forms of microscopy, these probes allow us to measure and control neuronal signals with spatial resolution and genetic specificity that already greatly surpass those of electrophysiology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Population Genomics</title>
      <link>/too2/new_geno/population/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/too2/new_geno/population/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Popilation Genetic Analysis  Pedigree Reconstruction Forward Simulation Population Structure Inference  Genotyping by Sequencing data analysis (GBS Analysis)  Base Callling Read Quality Contorl Adapter trimming Gerline SNO Detection Somatic SNV detection  Restriction Site Associated DNA Sequencing Data Analysis (RAD-seq Analysis)  Phylogenetic Inference SNP/SNV Annotation  Find more tools: OMICTOOLS   
Population genomics is the large-scale comparison of DNA sequences of populations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Protein Interactions</title>
      <link>/too2/new_proteo/interactions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/too2/new_proteo/interactions/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Protein Interactions Analysis  Protein-DNA Interaction Prediction Protein-RNA Interaction Prediction Pocket Detection Drug-target Interaction Prediction Protein-protein Interaction Prediction Protein-ligand Docking Protein-protein Docking  FRET Find more tools: OMICTOOLS   Protein Interactions Analysis Proteins interact with nucleic acids, other proteins, ligands, metal ions, to exert their biological functions. Mass-spectrometry and protein chips have revolutionized the field of proteomics and the study of protein interactions to a wider scale, which require specific tools for their analyses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RNA-Protein Interactions</title>
      <link>/too2/new_trans/rna_pro/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/too2/new_trans/rna_pro/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  CLIP-seq Analysis  Peak Calling Motif Discovery miRNA Target Site Detection  Ribo-seq Analysis  RNase Footprint Detection Ribosome P-site Localization Ribosome Stalling Prediction Translated ORF Prediction  Find more tools: OMICTOOLS   CLIP-seq Analysis Cross-Linking Immunoprecipitation associated to high-throughput sequencing (CLIP-seq) is a technique used to identify RNA directly bound to RNA-binding proteins across the entire transcriptome in cell or tissue samples. Recent technological and computational advances permit the analysis of many CLIP-seq samples simultaneously, allowing us to reveal the comprehensive network of RNA-protein interaction and to integrate it to other genome-wide analyses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brain Connectomics</title>
      <link>/too2/new_pheno/brain/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/too2/new_pheno/brain/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Connectivity Analysis  Functional Brain Connectivity Structural Brain Connectivity  Functional Magnetic Resonance Imaging (fMRI)  3D Image Surfacing  Diffusion Magnetic Resonance Imaging Analysis  Tractography  Neuron Tracing Find more tools: OMICTOOLS   Connectivity Analysis The functional organization of the brain is characterized by segregation and integration of information being processed. A central paradigm in modern neuroscience is that anatomical and functional connections between brain regions are organized in a way such that information processing is near optimal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DNA-Protein Interactions</title>
      <link>/too2/new_geno/dna_pro/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/too2/new_geno/dna_pro/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  HT-SELEX Analysis DNase-seq Analysis ChIP-seq Analysis  De novo assembly Peak calling Differential peak calling De novo motif discovery  Find more tools: OMICTOOLS   DNA-binding proteins are proteins that have DNA-binding domains and thus have a specific or general affinity for single- or double-stranded DNA. Sequence-specific DNA-binding proteins generally interact with the major groove of B-DNA, because it exposes more functional groups that identify a base pair.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Membrane Protein</title>
      <link>/too2/new_proteo/membrane/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/too2/new_proteo/membrane/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Membrane Protein Analysis  Membrane Protein-protein Docking Membrane Simulation Transmembrane Beta-barrel Prediction Transmembrane Helix Prediction Function Membrane Protein  FRAP Find more tools: OMICTOOLS   Membrane Protein Analysis Membrane and transmembrane proteins are key component of cell signaling. Their configuration, folding, or activity depend on several biochemical factors that can be predicted by specific software.
Membrane Protein-protein Docking Membrane Simulation Transmembrane Beta-barrel Prediction Transmembrane Helix Prediction Function Membrane Protein FRAP Top</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Non-Coding RNA</title>
      <link>/too2/new_trans/non_coding/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/too2/new_trans/non_coding/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Non-Coding RNA Analysis  miRNA Target Prediction miRNA Enrichment miRNA-disease Association Prediction RNAi Reagent Design High-throughput RNAi Screening  Small RNA sequencing Data analysis (sRNA-seq Analysis)  tRNA-derived RNA Annotation ncRNA Identification IsomiR detection nvRNA-related SNPS  miRNA Array analysis Find more tools: OMICTOOLS   Non-Coding RNA Analysis Noncoding RNAs (ncRNAs) accomplish a remarkable variety of biological functions. They regulate gene expression at the levels of transcription, RNA processing, and translation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Phylogenetic Data Analysis</title>
      <link>/too2/new_geno/phylogenetic/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/too2/new_geno/phylogenetic/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Popilation Genetic Analysis Phylogenetic inference Phylogenetic Network Construction Discrete Character Evolution Tumor Progression Tree Visualization Find more tools: OMIVTOOLS   
In biology, phylogenetics is the study of the evolutionary history and relationships among individuals or groups of organisms (e.g. species, or populations). These relationships are discovered through phylogenetic inference methods that evaluate observed heritable traits, such as DNA sequences or morphology under a model of evolution of these traits.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>