<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bms8110_p1 on CityU-Bioinformatics</title>
    <link>/tags/bms8110_p1/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Bms8110_p1 on CityU-Bioinformatics</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/bms8110_p1/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Functional analysis based on gene expression profiles suggested key signaling pathways in ESCC</title>
      <link>/tutorial/bms8110/escc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tutorial/bms8110/escc/</guid>
      <description>Student Project done by: LI Ying (54952422)
The slides can be downloaded here

Esophageal carcinoma Esophageal carcinoma arising from the esophagus—the food pipe that runs between the throat and the stomach.
Characteristics:  Common cancer: esophageal cancer was the eighth-most common cancer. Most common in China: half of all cancer cases occurring in China. Low survival rates: Five-year survival rates are around 13% to 18%.  The two main sub-types of the esophageal carcinoma:  Esophageal squamous-cell carcinoma (ESCC) Esophageal adenocarcinoma (EAC)  Sample collection  Microarray Data</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Genome-wide analysis of gene expression profiles for prioritization of dysregulated genes and pathways associated with the JQ1 treated lymphoblastic leukemia</title>
      <link>/tutorial/bms8110/jq1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tutorial/bms8110/jq1/</guid>
      <description>Student Project done by: Abhimanyu Thakur (54163550)
The slides can be downloaded here
Acute Lymphoblastic Leukemia  Neoplastic disease which results from a mutation in a single lymphoid progenitor cell at one of several discrete stages of development B Cell or T Cell Most common childhood acute leukemia, ~80% Incidence in adults ~20% Bimodal distribution of occurrence: Peak at age 2-5 &amp;amp; Second augmented incidence after age 50  Pathogenesis Acquired Genetic Change in Chromosome</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JUNB is involved in TGFβ induced cancer invasion</title>
      <link>/tutorial/bms8110/junb/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tutorial/bms8110/junb/</guid>
      <description>Student Project done by: HUANG Hao (54893350)
The slides can be downloaded here
In breast cancer, SMAD has rare mutation and weak capability of DNA binding, usually interact with other co-factors or transcription factors to bind to DNA.
Background  In breast cancer, SMAD has rare mutation and weak capability of DNA binding, usually interact with other co-factors or transcription factors to bind to DNA. Transforming growth factor-β (TGFβ) plays dual role during tumor progression——tumor suppressor or tumor promoter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rnomic Study of Colon Epithelial Cell Infection and Association with Ulcerative Colitis</title>
      <link>/tutorial/bms8110/rnomic/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tutorial/bms8110/rnomic/</guid>
      <description>Student Project done by: Liu Liangzhe, Fiona (54465134)
The slides can be downloaded here
Ulcerative Colitis  One type of inflammatory bowel disease (IBD) Bloody stools, mucous discharge, lower abdominal pain Chronic, lifelong condition Treated with chemotherapy, steroid and immunosuppression Associate with pathogenic bacteria infection  RNA seq data from published paper Differential expression analysis using DEseq2 Gene Sets Enrichment using Msic_c5 Collection Chemokine and CXCR  A family of chemotactic cytokines Cell response to infection induce chemotaxis leukocyte activation granule exocytosis up-regulation of respiratory burst activity Link to various of chronic inflammatory disease  Citation: http://pharmacy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sox4 ChIP-Seq data analysis</title>
      <link>/tutorial/bms8110/sox4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tutorial/bms8110/sox4/</guid>
      <description>Student Project done by: HU, Jianyang (54863843)
The slides can be downloaded here
Overview of ChIP-Seq analysis For ChIP-Seq, single-end (50bp) FASTQ reads were mapped to mouse genome mm10 (GRCm38, Dec/2011). Peaks 2,207 narrow peak regions and 2207 summits.
Motif discovery and Distribution of Sox4 binding sites by CEAS analysis Sox4 Target gene’s associated peaks prediction by BETA-minus analysis 1940 lines were identified using BETA-minus analysis in Galaxy/Cristrome. Among these 1940 lines and 1004 of them are located within promoter region (1000 bp upstream of TSS).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>