<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>metabolomics on CityU-Bioinformatics</title>
    <link>/tags/metabolomics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in metabolomics on CityU-Bioinformatics</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/metabolomics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Drug Discovery</title>
      <link>/too2/new_meta/drug/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/too2/new_meta/drug/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Drug Discovery  Drug-drug interaction prediction  DDI-CPI | Drug-Drug Interaction via Chemical-Protein Interactome Hierarchical RNNs model-based DDI extraction  Ligand-based Virtual Screening  FTrees | Feature Trees Frog | FRee On line druG conformation generation  Drug Repositioning  DRRS | Drug repositioning recommendation system MANTRA | Mode of Action by NeTwoRk Analysis  Chemical Toxicity  ChemDes | Chemical toxicity : Drug design  Molecular editors  Bioclipse | Molecule editors : Drug design MCCE | Multi-Conformation Continuum Electrostatics   Find more tools: OMICTOOLS   Drug Discovery In the fields of medicine, biotechnology and pharmacology, drug discovery is the process by which new candidate medications are discovered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lipidomics</title>
      <link>/too2/new_meta/lipidomics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/too2/new_meta/lipidomics/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Lipidomics Databases  LIPID MAPS | LIPID Metabolites And Pathways Strategy LipidBlast | Lipidomic spectral libraries : Lipidomics databases  MS-based untargeted lipidomics  LipidMatch | Lipid identification : MS-based untargeted lipidomics Quantinetix | Image signal quantification : Mass spectrometry  MS-based targeted lipidomics  MRMPROBS | Multiple Reaction Monitoring-based PROBabilistic System MRM-DIFF | Multiple Reaction Monitoring-based DIFFerential  Find more tools: OMICTOOLS   Lipidomics or profiling specific classes of lipids biomarkers also provides a unique opportunity to identify diseases other than cancer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Metabolic Engineering</title>
      <link>/too2/new_meta/engineer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/too2/new_meta/engineer/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Biological Steps  Constraint based methods  fastcore COBRA Toolbox | COnstraints Based Reconstruction and Analysis  Metabolic pathway prediction  EC-BLAST RetroPath  Strain design  Biopathway Predictor cRegMCSs | constrained regulatory MCSs  Thermodynamics  SSTMap | Solvation Structure and Thermodynamic Mapping von Bertalanffy   13C-fluxomics  COBRA Toolbox | COnstraints Based Reconstruction and Analysis C13 | 13C-fluxomics : Metabolomics  Find more tools: OMICTOOLS   Growing concerns over limited fossil resources and associated environmental problems are motivating the development of sustainable processes for the production of chemicals, fuels and materials from renewable resources.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Metabolic Profiles</title>
      <link>/too2/new_meta/profiles/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/too2/new_meta/profiles/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Metabolic profiles analysis  Metabolic Network analysis  BLASTX PiMP | Polyomics integrated Metabolomics Pipeline  Metabolite enrichment analysis  MetScape | Data integration : Mass spectrometry analysis FELLA | Metabolite enrichment analysis   MS-based untargeted Metabolomics  mGWAS  MWASTools | mGWAS RegScan   NMR-based Metabolomics/MS-based targeted metabolomics  Spectral corrections  NMRPipe NMRPro  Spectral deconvolution  NMRPipe BATMAN | Bayesian AuTomated Metabolite Analyser for NMR data  Chemometric analysis  MetaboAnalyst speaq | spectrum alignment and quantitation  Metabolite identification  W4M | Workflow4Metabolomics MetaboAnalyst   Find more tools: OMICTOOLS   Metabolic profiles analysis The further development of spectroscopic and spectrometric tools for high throughput analyses of selected biochemical pathways is crucial to the acquisition of metabolome data sets of sufficient quality for metabonomics and metabolomics.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>