<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Comprehensive on CityU-Bioinformatics</title>
    <link>/journal/comprehensive/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Comprehensive on CityU-Bioinformatics</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/journal/comprehensive/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Aerican Journal of Human Genetics (AJHG)</title>
      <link>/journal/comprehensive/american-journal-of-human-genetics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/journal/comprehensive/american-journal-of-human-genetics/</guid>
      <description>Official Website
AJHG provides a record of research and review relating to heredity in humans and to the application of genetic principles in medicine and public policy, as well as in related areas of molecular and cell biology. Topics explored by AJHG include behavioral genetics, biochemical genetics, clinical genetics, cytogenetics, dysmorphology, gene therapy, genetic counseling, genetic epidemiology, genomics, immunogenetics, molecular genetics, neurogenetics, and population genetics.
AJHG welcomes submissions of articles and reports on timely subjects concerning all aspects of human genetics, including studies of model organisms that are of direct relevance to human genetics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cancer Cell</title>
      <link>/journal/comprehensive/cancer-cell/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/journal/comprehensive/cancer-cell/</guid>
      <description>Official Website
Cancer Cell provides a high-profile forum to promote major advances in cancer research and oncology. The primary criterion for considering manuscripts is whether the studies provide major advances into answering important questions relevant to naturally occurring cancers. Cancer Cell particularly welcomes translational research.
Cancer Cell is also interested in publishing clinical investigations, in particular those that lead to establishing new paradigms in the treatment, diagnosis, or prevention of cancers; those that provide important insights into cancer biology beyond what has been revealed by preclinical studies; and those that are mechanism-based proof-of-principle clinical studies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cell Research</title>
      <link>/journal/comprehensive/cell-research/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/journal/comprehensive/cell-research/</guid>
      <description>Official Website
Cell Research (CR) publishes original research results that are of unusual significance or broad conceptual or technical advances in all areas of life sciences, as long as the study is closely related to molecular and cell biology. The journal has an international authorship and a broad scope in basic research including:
 Cell growth, differentiation &amp;amp; apoptosis Signal transduction Stem cell biology &amp;amp; development Chromatin, epigenetics &amp;amp; transcription RNA biology Structural &amp;amp; molecular biology Cancer biology Immunity &amp;amp; molecular pathogenesis Molecular &amp;amp; cellular neuroscience Plant molecular &amp;amp; cell biology Genomics &amp;amp; proteomics  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cell</title>
      <link>/journal/comprehensive/cell/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/journal/comprehensive/cell/</guid>
      <description>Official Website
Cell publishes findings of unusual significance in any area of experimental biology, including but not limited to cell biology, molecular biology, neuroscience, immunology, virology and microbiology, cancer, human genetics, systems biology, signaling, and disease mechanisms and therapeutics. The basic criterion for considering papers is whether the results provide significant conceptual advances into, or raise provocative questions and hypotheses regarding, an interesting and important biological question. In addition to primary research articles in four formats, Cell features review and opinion articles on recent research advances and issues of interest to its broad readership in the Leading Edge section.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Current Biology</title>
      <link>/journal/comprehensive/current-biology/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/journal/comprehensive/current-biology/</guid>
      <description>Official Website
Current Biology is a general journal that publishes original research across all areas of biology together with an extensive and varied set of editorial sections. A primary aim of the journal is to foster communication across fields of biology, both by publishing important findings of general interest from diverse fields and through highly accessible editorial articles that explicitly aim to inform non-specialists. Current Biology publishes papers reporting findings in any area of biology that have sufficient claim to be of general interest—this could be, for example, because the advance is important for a specific field, or because it is intrinsically of wide interest to biologists generally.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Genome Biology</title>
      <link>/journal/comprehensive/genome-biology/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/journal/comprehensive/genome-biology/</guid>
      <description>Official Website
Genome Biology publishes outstanding research in all areas of biology and biomedicine studied from a genomic and post-genomic perspective.
Genome Biology covers all areas of biology and biomedicine studied from a genomic and post-genomic perspective. Content includes research, new methods and software tools, and reviews, opinions and commentaries. Areas covered include, but are not limited to: sequence analysis; bioinformatics; insights into molecular, cellular and organismal biology; functional genomics; epigenomics; population genomics; proteomics; comparative biology and evolution; systems and network biology; genome editing and engineering; genomics of disease; and clinical genomics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Genome Research</title>
      <link>/journal/comprehensive/genome-research/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/journal/comprehensive/genome-research/</guid>
      <description>Official Website
Launched in 1995, Genome Research is an international, continuously published, peer-reviewed journal that publishes studies on the structure, function, biology, and evolution of genomes of all organisms, with a long-standing emphasis on genome-scale analyses, chromatin structure and function, epigenomics, systems genetics, and proteomics. They also feature gene discoveries that provide novel insights and reports of high-throughput experimental and computational approaches.
In addition to these core areas, the journal is now particularly interested in the following areas: comprehensive characterization of genome sequence variation</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Molecular Cell</title>
      <link>/journal/comprehensive/molecular-cell/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/journal/comprehensive/molecular-cell/</guid>
      <description>Official Website
Molecular Cell is a peer-reviewed scientific journal that covers research on cell biology at the molecular level, with an emphasis on new mechanistic insights. It was established in 1997 and is published two times per month.
The journal covers core cellular processes, including:
 DNA replication, recombination, and repair Chromatin biology and genome organization Transcription RNA processing and decay Non-coding RNA function Translation Protein folding, modification, and quality control Signal transduction pathways Cell cycle and checkpoints Cell death Autophagy Metabolism  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Molecular Systems Biology</title>
      <link>/journal/comprehensive/molecular-systems-biology/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/journal/comprehensive/molecular-systems-biology/</guid>
      <description>Official Website
Molecular Cell is a peer-reviewed scientific journal that covers research on cell biology at the molecular level, with an emphasis on new mechanistic insights. It was established in 1997 and is published two times per month.
The journal covers core cellular processes, including:
 DNA replication, recombination, and repair Chromatin biology and genome organization Transcription RNA processing and decay Non-coding RNA function Translation Protein folding, modification, and quality control Signal transduction pathways Cell cycle and checkpoints Cell death Autophagy Metabolism  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nature Biotechnology</title>
      <link>/journal/comprehensive/nature-biotechnology/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/journal/comprehensive/nature-biotechnology/</guid>
      <description>Official Website
Nature Biotechnology is a peer reviewed scientific journal published monthly by the Nature Publishing Group. The chief editor is Andrew Marshall who is part of an in-house team of editors. The focus of the journal is biotechnology including research results and the commercial business sector of this field. Coverage includes the related biological, biomedical, agricultural and environmental sciences. Also of interest are the commercial, political, legal, and societal influences that affect this field.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nature Cell Biology</title>
      <link>/journal/comprehensive/nature-cell-biology/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/journal/comprehensive/nature-cell-biology/</guid>
      <description>Official Website
Nature Cell Biology publishes papers of the highest quality from all areas of cell biology, encouraging those that shed light on the mechanisms underlying fundamental cell biological processes.
The journal&amp;rsquo;s scope is broad and specific areas of interest include, but are not limited to:
 Autophagy Cancer biology Cell adhesion and migration Cell cycle and growth Cell death Chromatin and epigenetics Cytoskeletal dynamics Developmental biology DNA replication and repair Mechanisms of human disease Mechanobiology Membrane traffic and dynamics Metabolism Nuclear organization and dynamics Organelle biology Proteolysis and quality control RNA biology Signal transduction Stem cell biology  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nature Chemical Biology</title>
      <link>/journal/comprehensive/nature-chemical-biology/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/journal/comprehensive/nature-chemical-biology/</guid>
      <description>Official Website
The publishing focus of Nature Chemical Biology is a forum for original research and commentary in Chemical-biology. Published topics encompass concepts and research methods in chemistry, biology, and related disciplines with the end result of controlling biological systems at the molecular level. Authors (contributors) are chemical biologists, also chemists involved in interdisciplinary research between chemistry and biology, along with biologists who produce research results in understanding and controlling biological processes at the molecular level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nature Genetics</title>
      <link>/journal/comprehensive/nature-genetics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/journal/comprehensive/nature-genetics/</guid>
      <description>Official Website
Nature Genetics publishes the very highest quality research in genetics. It encompasses genetic and functional genomic studies on human and plant traits and on other model organisms. Current emphasis is on the genetic basis for common and complex diseases and on the functional mechanism, architecture and evolution of gene networks, studied by experimental perturbation.
Integrative genetic topics comprise, but are not limited to:
 Genes in the pathology of human disease Molecular analysis of simple and complex genetic traits Cancer genetics Agricultural genomics Developmental genetics Regulatory variation in gene expression Strategies and technologies for extracting function from genomic data Pharmacological genomics Genome evolution  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nature Medicine</title>
      <link>/journal/comprehensive/nature-medicine/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/journal/comprehensive/nature-medicine/</guid>
      <description>Official Website
The journal was established in 1995 and is published by the Nature Publishing Group. As with other Nature journals, there is no external editorial board, with editorial decisions being made by an in-house team, although peer review by external expert referees forms a part of the review process.
Original research articles published in Nature Medicine range from basic findings that have clear implications for disease pathogenesis and therapy to the earliest phases of human investigation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nature Methods</title>
      <link>/journal/comprehensive/nature-methods/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/journal/comprehensive/nature-methods/</guid>
      <description>Official Website
Nature Methods is a forum for the publication of novel methods and significant improvements to tried-and-tested basic research techniques in the life sciences. This monthly publication is aimed at a broad, interdisciplinary audience of academic and industry researchers actively involved in laboratory practice. It provides them with new tools to conduct their research and places a strong emphasis on the immediate practical relevance of the work presented.
The journal publishes primary research papers as well as overviews of recent technical and methodological developments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nature Protocols</title>
      <link>/journal/comprehensive/nature-protocols/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/journal/comprehensive/nature-protocols/</guid>
      <description>Official Website
Nature Protocols is an online journal of high-quality peer-reviewed protocols for researchers. Protocols are commissioned by the editors or submitted by authors as Presubmission Enquiries. They are presented in a &amp;lsquo;recipe&amp;rsquo; style, providing step-by-step descriptions of procedures that users can take to the lab and immediately apply in their own research. All protocols have been proven to work already, having been used to generate data reported in published research papers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nucleic Acid Research</title>
      <link>/journal/comprehensive/nucleic-acid-research/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/journal/comprehensive/nucleic-acid-research/</guid>
      <description>Official Website
Nucleic Acids Research ( NAR ) publishes the results of leading edge research into physical, chemical, biochemical and biological aspects of nucleic acids and proteins involved in nucleic acid metabolism and/or interactions. It enables the rapid publication of papers under the following categories: Chemistry and synthetic biology; Computational biology; Gene regulation, chromatin and epigenetics; Genome integrity, repair and replication; Genomics; Molecular biology; Nucleic acid enzymes; RNA and Structural biology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plos Biology</title>
      <link>/journal/comprehensive/plos-biology/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/journal/comprehensive/plos-biology/</guid>
      <description>Official Website
PLOS Biology features works of exceptional significance, originality, and relevance in all areas of biological science, from molecules to ecosystems, including works at the interface of other disciplines, such as chemistry, medicine, and mathematics. They also welcome data-driven meta-research articles that evaluate and aim to improve the standards of research in the life sciences and beyond. Their audience is the international scientific community as well as educators, policy makers, patient advocacy groups, and interested members of the public around the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Systematic Biology</title>
      <link>/journal/comprehensive/systematic-biology/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/journal/comprehensive/systematic-biology/</guid>
      <description>Official Website
Systematic Biology is the bimonthly journal of the Society of Systematic Biologists. Papers for the journal are original contributions to the theory, principles, and methods of systematics as well as phylogeny, evolution, morphology, biogeography, paleontology, genetics, and the classification of all living things. A Points of View section offers a forum for discussion, while book reviews and announcements of general interest are also featured.
Systematic Biology is listed by the following services:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>